livingfrugal.com 2013-08-05

# Living Frugal | Privacy Policy

At Living Frugal, we want to respect your privacy. In return, you consent to our privacy policy terms. We strive to offer you a great place to learn how to save money and produce financial goals, without infringing on your privacy. Because each visit is meant to be fulfilling and constructive, Living Frugal gathers information to create a unique visit for each user.

Living Frugal collects some personal information for user experience, submission and feedback. However, the personal information will not be used for reasons other than the intended purpose unless you give approval.

Your Account Information: If you use Facebook to login, we will keep record of your personal information, including your email address and name. Through this, we are able to give our users the best possible experience.

User Submissions: Any submissions you contribute to Living Frugal may be stored or publically displayed. When you submit through Facebook, this includes your first and last name, profile picture and your current location. However, you can edit your account settings to not display these details. Submissions include anything you post to Living Frugal or your public profile.

Unsubscribe: To unsubscribe from Livng Frugal mailling lists please use [www.LivingFrugal.com/unsubscribe/](http://www.livingfrugal.com/unsubscribe/).

Feedback: Living Frugal will make record of personal information and other content when you offer us feedback, ask questions or leave a complaint. This way, we are able to address user issues and compliments quickly and effectively.

User Activity: In order to best suit our users, we record information like your browser type, IP address, searches, timestamp information and the pages you viewed. This allows us to make site improvements and see what parts of Living Frugal are being most used.

Use Of Cookies: Living Frugal utilizes cookies to provide insight for site improvements. Cookies are small pieces of information that are sent to your computer while on our site. You may disable your cookies through your browser settings. However in doing so, you may diminish your Living Frugal use.

Information Transfer: Third-party advertising companies own the advertisements on Living Frugal. They may take information about your Living Frugal interaction to produce ads that are a better fit for your needs. The third parties may receive submissions you make through the website, which may be published on their site. This information includes your account name, but not other personal information unless it was in the submission itself.

When these submissions are used, they may not abide by our privacy policy. Even with a relationship with these third parties, they follow their own privacy policy. Do not include information in your submission that you wish to keep private.

Your information may be shared with Living Frugal’s affiliates, including our parent company, business ventures, or companies that are under current or future common control. When information is shared, the companies are compelled to honor our privacy policy.

Privacy Policy Terms And Changes: At any time, we may make changes to this privacy policy. If and when this happens, there will be updated versions posted on this page. If changes are made regarding your personal information, you will be notified via email.
